const questions = [
  {
    question: "Another name for Loop 343?",
    answer: "Lamar",
    choices: ["Mopac", "The Drag", "Research Blvd"],
  },
  {
    question: "What does Mopac stand for?",
    answer: "Missouri Pacific",
    choices: ["Motor Primary Accesess", " MOP Access Corridor", "MoPac"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which road runs East/West?",
    answer: "Barton Springs",
    choices: ["Congress", "1st Street", "Red River"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which is not a Bar District??",
    answer: "Zilker Park",
    choices: ["Sixth Street", "Rainey Street", "Rock Rose"],
  },
  {
    question: "Where is ACL held?",
    answer: "Zilker Park",
    choices: ["Sixth Street", "Auditorium Shores", "Rock Rose"],
  },
  {
    question: "Where does the UT basketball team player?",
    answer: "Frank Erwin Center",
    choices: ["UT Arena", "Circuits of the America", "Austin High School"],
  },
  {
    question: "What road leads up to the State Capitol?",
    answer: "Congress",
    choices: ["Lamar", "1st street", "Sixth Street"],
  },
  {
    question: "What is the InterState highway that passing through Austin?",
    answer: "I-35",
    choices: ["I-290", "I-45", "I-130"],
  },
  {
    question: "Tallest building in Austin?",
    answer: "The Independent",
    choices: ["Frost Tower", "Austonian", "Fairmont"],
  },
  {
    question: "Which animal live under the Congress bridge?",
    answer: "Bats",
    choices: ["Cats", "Dogs", "Crows"],
  },
  
];


